Guide to the Washington Office on Africa Records - Addendum A
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Topical Files, Series III
  - Advocacy Work and Topical Files
    - Sapes Book Catalogue, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 509)
    - African Development Foundation, 1994-96 (Box 45, Folder 510)
    - Conflict Resolution, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 511)
    - Foreign Aid Attack, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 512)
    - GSP/GATT/Trade Africa, 1994-1995 (Box 46, Folder 513,514)
    - Hearing: 10/04/94; "South Africa since the Historic Elections", 1994 (Box 46, Folder 515)
    - House Hearing: 04/20/94; "US Policy Towards SA in the eve of the elections", 1994 (Box 46, Folder 516)
    - Legislation: HR 4317; Rwanda, Designation of Protected Status (Temporary), 1994 (Box 46, Folder 517)
    - Legislation: HR 453; Situation in Rwanda, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 518)
    - Senate Hearing: 07/26/94; "US Response to the crisis in Rwanda/ Central Africa", 1994 (Box 46, Folder 519)
    - Legislation: HR 4541; African Conflict Resolution Act, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 520)
    - Legislation S207; Catastrophe in Rwanda, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 521)
    - Legislation HR4317; Protected Status for Rwandan Students in the US, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 522)
    - Penny/ Kashish Amendment to HR3725, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 523)
    - Senate Hearing "Global Landmine Crisis", 1994 (Box 46, Folder 524)
    - S 2475-African Conflict Resolution Act, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 525)
    - House Hearing "Foreign aid Reform", 1994 Feb (Box 46, Folder 526)
    - Senate Hearing "Foreign Aid Reform", 1994 (Box 46, Folder 527)
    - House Hearing "Foreign Aid Reform", 1994 Feb (Box 46, Folder 528)
    - Conflict Resolution, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 529)
    - House Hearing; "Conflict Res. In Africa Recent Development", 1994 Jun 8 (Box 46, Folder 530)
    - Senate Hearing "African Conflict Resolution", 1994 Sep 28 (Box 46, Folder 531)
    - Legislation: HR 3765; Peace, Prosperity, and Democracy Act, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 532)
    - Legislation: S 1856; Peace, Prosperity and Democracy Act, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 533)
    - S 1060/HR 2564-Silence America, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 534)
    - Trade/ Development, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 535)
    - Clinton Administration (1), 1995 (Box 47, Folder 536)
    - Clinton Administration(2) (Box 47, Folder 537)
    - US and Economy, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 538)
    - US and Foreign Aid, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 539)
    - US and Africa, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 540)
    - USAID, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 541)
    - US- General, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 542-542c)
    - US- general (Politics), 1995 (Box 47, Folder 543)
    - US Budget, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 544, 544a)
    - USAID, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 545)
    - WB/ IMF, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 546)
    - US Social Issues/ Human Rights, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 547)
    - US in Peacekeeping Efforts, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 548)
    - Race Relations, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 549)
    - State Dept, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 550)
    - Unions, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 551, 551a)
    - US Immigration, 1995-1996 (Box 47a, Folder 552)
    - US Lobbyists, 1995 (Box 47a, Folder 553)
    - Advocacy Kit, 1995 (Box 47a, Folder 554)
    - US Federal Budget for FY 1994, 1995 (Box 47a, Folder 555)
    - US Environment, 1995-1997 (Box 48, Folder 556)
    - USAID-South Africa, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 557)
    - US and Foreign Policy and Diplomacy, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 558)
    - Peacekeeping, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 559)
    - Holland Committee on Southern Africa, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 560)
    - Documents/Publications, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 561)
    - Documents/Publication, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 562)
    - US Actions, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 563, 564)
    - Africa's Problems... African Initiatives (Box 48, Folder 565)
    - Nancy Kassenbaun (R-KA), Chair African Affairs Subcommittee, 1995-1996 (Box 48, Folder 566)
    - Aid, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 567)
    - Congressional Contact Report; Congressional Black Caucus; Congressional Visits, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 568)
    - President Bill Clinton and Cabinet, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 569)
    - Department of State, 1995-1996 (Box 49, Folder 570)
    - Congressional Progressive Caucus; Barney Frank( D-MA,4), 1995 (Box 49, Folder 571)
    - Miscellaneous papers concerning USAID in a brown folder, 1995-1996 (Box 49, Folder 572-576)
    - Silence America Legislation, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 578)
    - House Foreign Operations Appropriations FY96, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 579)
    - HR1561-American Overseas Interest Act; HR1562-Foreign Affairs Agencies Consolidation, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 580)
    - The Progressive Review, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 581)
    - S908- State Dept. Authorizing and Appropriations(1996-99), 1995 (Box 50, Folder 582)
    - Senate Foreign Operations Appropriations, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 583)
    - Congressional '96, 1995-96 (Box 50, Folder 584)
    - African Conflict Resolution Act-Progressive Report, 1995-1996 (Box 50, Folder 585)
    - Clinton Admin: William Clinton, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 586)
    - 104th Congress, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 587,587a)
    - Senate Appropriations, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 588)
    - McConnell Foreign Aid Bill, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 589)
    - North Carolina -Prelim. Contacts, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 590)
    - Committee on Foreign Relations -Women in Africa, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 591)
    - House IR Subcommittee Hearing: Liberia, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 592)
    - House IR Subcommittee Hearing: Liberia, 1996 (Box 50a, Folder 593)
    - House Subcommittee Hearing: New Perspectives on Africa, 1996 (Box 50a, Folder 594)
    - House Hearing; Current Human Rights Situation in Africa, 1996 (Box 50a, Folder 595,596)
    - House Hearing; Paul Niefert Statement on USAID, 1996 (Box 50a, Folder 597)
    - House Hearing; Crisis in Liberia, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 598)
    - Senate Hearing; US Development Assistance In Africa, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 599)
    - Senate Hearing; Angolan Peace Process, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 600,601)
    - Trade; House Subcommittee Hearing(08/01/96), 1996 (Box 51, Folder 602,603)
    - US Policy/Congressional Action, 1996-97 (Box 51, Folder 604)
    - Congressional Testimonies on Assistance to Africa, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 605)
    - ACOA Letter to the Senate, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 606)
    - Loose materials on assistance to Africa USAID (Box 51, Folder 607)
    - Cities Update (Dept. of Interior), 1996-1997 (Box 51, Folder 608)
    - USAID Publications, 1996-1997 (Box 51, Folder 609,609a)
    - 105th Congress, 1996-1997 (Box 51, Folder 610)
    - US General, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 611)
    - US and Africa, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 612)
    - African American Issues, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 613)
    - USAID-Agency for International Development, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 614)
    - US Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 52, Folder 615,616)
    - US and Foreign Aid, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 617,618)
    - Clinton Administration, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 619)
    - 104th Congress, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 620)
    - US and Economy, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 621)
    - Electronic Communications, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 622)
    - Elections, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 623)
    - US and Immigration, 1996-1997 (Box 52, Folder 624)
    - US and Foreign Policy Diplomacy, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 625)
    - US Lobbyists, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 626)
    - US and Military/ Arms, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 627)
    - US General Politics, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 628)
    - Race Relations, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 629)
    - US and Social Issues/ Human Rights, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 630)
    - Unions, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 631)
    - State Department, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 632)
    - US Trade with Sub Saharan Africa, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 633)
    - US and United Nations, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 634)
    - Women, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 635)
    - IMF/ World Bank and other International financial and trade institutions, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 636)
    - Relief Agencies, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 637)
    - Human Rights/ Repression, 1996-1997 (Box 54, Folder 638,639)
    - General Background/ Miscellaneous, 1996-1997 (Box 54, Folder 640)
    - Conflict Resolution, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 641)
    - Monitoring the Right, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 642)
    - Conflict Resolution in Africa Interaction/ USAID, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 643,644)
    - White House Briefing FY97 International Affairs Budget, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 645)
    - Howard University, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 646)
    - Loose Papers Concerning WOA/APIC advocacy work, 1996-1998 (Box 54, Folder 647)
    - Fast Facts Resource Guides, 1996-1997 (Box 55, Folder 648)
    - Technical, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 649)
    - Terrorism, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 650)
    - War Crimes, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 651)
    - UN- general, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 652)
    - Torture Victims Relief act, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 653)
    - FY97 Budget, 1996-97 (Box 55, Folder 654)
    - 105 Congress-Africa, 1996-1997 (Box 55, Folder 655)
    - Torture Victims Relief Act, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 656)
    - Campaign '96 and Africa, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 657)
    - IR Committee: Africa Subcommittee, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 658)
    - H.Con. Re.142 Mauritania, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 659,660)
    - HR 3540-FY97 Appropriations, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 662)
    - Clinton Admin: Warren Christopher, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 663)
    - Clinton Admin: miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 664)
    - General Legislature, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 665)
    - Congressional Black Caucus, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 666)
    - House IR Committee, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 667)
    - Senate for Rel Committee:Africa Affairs Committee, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 668)
    - Senate Appropriations Committee: For. Op. Subcommittee, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 669)
    - House Appropriations Committee For. Op. et al Subcommittee, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 670)
    - House Africa Subc'tee Hearings (09/18/97), 1997 (Box 56, Folder 671)
    - Beth's Originals, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 672)
    - Nigerian lobbying/ PR in US, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 673)
    - Zaire Hearing (04/08/97), 1997 (Box 56, Folder 674)
    - US and Africa, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 675)
    - Clinton Administration, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 676)
    - USAID, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 677)
    - US Congress, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 678)
    - G-7 Denver Summit, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 679)
    - US Foreign Policy, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 680)
    - Free Labour World, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 681)
    - Gov't Politics, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 682)
    - US and Immigration, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 683)
    - Landmines-Evans, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 684)
    - Leahy-Landmines, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 685)
    - Loose Papers mainly concerning development aid (Box 57, Folder 686-689)
    - Loose Papers mainly concerning development aid (Box 58, Folder 690-692)
    - Peace Corps (Box 58, Folder 693)
    - US Policy, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 694)
    - Race Relations, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 695)
    - US Social, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 696)
    - US Social Issues: Human Rights, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 697)
    - US State Department, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 698)
    - US-UN Relations, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 699)
    - African Immigration- Smithsonian, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 700)
    - Presby-Mobil/ Eg. Guinea, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 701,702)
    - Refugee Women-GTU, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 703)
    - WNA Drafts, VOL.21 NO 3, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 704)
    - Miscellaneous pamphlets, articles etc, On Southern Africa (Box 59, Folder 705-708)
    - US Administration, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 709)
    - US Affirmative Action, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 710)
    - USAID, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 711)
    - African American Issues, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 712)
    - Congressional Info (Misc), 1997 (Box 59, Folder 713)
    - Foreign Aid, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 714)
    - Foreign Aid Budget-FY98, 1997-1998 (Box 60, Folder 715,716)
    - Congressional Visits/Calls-1997(July) (Box 60, Folder 717)
    - Legislative Updates 1997 (105th Congress) (Box 60, Folder 718)
    - Congressional Visits/Calls-1997(Jan-June) (Box 60, Folder 719)
    - G7 Summit Denver (June 20-22, 1997) (Box 60, Folder 720)
    - International Criminal Court (ICC), 1997 (Box 60, Folder 721)
    - Great Lakes Region- general, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 722)
    - Folder Containing WOA advocacy work, 1997 Apr (Box 60, Folder 723)
    - Senate/ House Material, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 724)
    - 105th Congress - Legislative Update, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 725)
    - Africa Peace Committee- Peace Tour, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 726)
    - Mailings, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 727)
    - US Budget, 1997, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 728,728a)
    - Interaction, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 729)
  - Files on Individual Representatives and Senators
    - Sonny Callahan, Ala (Box 61, Folder 730)
    - Jesse Helms, 1994-1996 (Box 61, Folder 731)
    - Ileana Ros-Lehtinen -FL, 18); House IR Committee, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 732)
    - Mitch McConnell (R-KY); Senate Appropriations Committee, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 733)
    - Mark Hatfield (R-OR),Chair; Senate Appropriations Committee, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 734)
    - Jesse Helms (R-NC), Chair Senate For. Rel. Committee, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 735)
    - Russell Feingold (D-WI); Senate For Rel. Committee, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 736)
    - Patrick Leahy (D-VT); Senate Appropriations Committee, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 737)
    - Carol Moseley-Braun (D-IL); Senate Banking Committee, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 738)
    - Donald Payne (D-NJ, 10); CBC, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 739)
    - Cynthia McKinney (D-GA, 11); CBC, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 740)
    - William Jefferson (D-LA, 2); CBC, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 741)
    - Charles Wilson (D-TX, 2); House Appropriations Committee, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 742)
    - Senator Carol Moseley- Braun (D-IL); CBC, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 743)
    - Newt Gingrich, 1994-96 (Box 61, Folder 744)
    - Donald Payne, NJ; House IR Committee, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 745)